greenerideal.com 2011-08-27

# Greener Ideal Privacy Policy | Greener Ideal

* * *

**Email Addresses**   
You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the monthly newsletter sign-up on our website. We will never share your email with any third party. We don't currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us though our contact form.

**Ownership of Information**   
Greener Ideal is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Comments/Message Boards**   
Greener Ideal contains a comment sections. We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce "comment spam." These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies, Web Beacons, and Similar Technologies**   
Greener Ideal may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to manage users' site preferences and ensure the site's functionality. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**   
Greener Ideal and its advertisers may also use ad network providers and other service providers. These providers may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their content and advertisements, using data gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience.

**Traffic Reports**   
Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**   
We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Greener.Ideal may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Links**   
Greener Ideal frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Greener Ideal

**Notification of Changes**   
When Greener Ideal makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**   
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
